parkwhiz.com 2014-02-10

# Privacy Policy | Guaranteed Parking - ParkWhiz

ParkWhiz.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

## What personally identifiable information does ParkWhiz.com collect from me?

ParkWhiz.com may collect information in several ways. ParkWhiz may ask you for personal information at times, including (but not limited to) when you personalize your parking preferences and register, make parking reservations using ParkWhiz.com and/or when you report a problem with one of our sites or services. ParkWhiz.com also occasionally asks users to complete surveys that we use for internal research. Wherever ParkWhiz.com collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

## What are cookies and how does ParkWhiz.com use them?

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, ParkWhiz.com may use cookies to store and sometimes track your information. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and may be stored on your computer's hard drive. 

Generally, we use cookies to: 

  * Store your personalized settings for items such as reservation and mobile preferences.
  * Determine whether you are using a public computer so that any ParkWhiz settings changed while using a public computer do not affect the next user's ability to use ParkWhiz.
  * To estimate our audience size. Each browser accessing ParkWhiz.com may be given a cookie that is then used to determine the extent of repeat usage and determine on an aggregate basis, which features of ParkWhiz are used. In order to gather these aggregate data, ParkWhiz may use cookies served by third parties.
  * Measure certain traffic patterns; track the areas of ParkWhiz.com's network of Web sites you have visited, track the Web site through which you came to ParkWhiz.com and your visiting patterns in the aggregate. We use this research to understand how our users' habits are similar or different from one another so that we can make each new experience on ParkWhiz.com a better one. We may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will see on our sites.
  * ParkWhiz.com also collects IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers.

## Who is collecting information?

When you are on a ParkWhiz.com site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information for use by ParkWhiz.com alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. Some ParkWhiz.com services may be offered in conjunction with a partner company. In order to provide this service to you, it may be necessary for us to share your personal information with our partner company. In such cases you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service. 

Please be aware that ParkWhiz.com advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Web sites linked to ParkWhiz.com are not covered by this privacy statement. 

## With whom does ParkWhiz.com share my information?

As a general rule, ParkWhiz.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed. 

**Business Partners & Sponsors:** ParkWhiz.com may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but this is specifically described to you prior to data collection or prior to transferring the data. If personally identifying data about you will be shared, we will tell you before we collect or transfer the data. 

**Third Party Data & Data in the Aggregate:** Under confidentiality agreements, ParkWhiz.com may match user information with third party data. Also, ParkWhiz.com discloses aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. 

**Tell a Friend:** If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. ParkWhiz, Inc. stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at privacy@parkwhiz.com to request that we remove this information from our database. 

**Other:** Under confidentiality agreements, ParkWhiz.com may match user information with third party data. Also, ParkWhiz.com discloses aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes. 

## What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?

If you choose to register with ParkWhiz (become a **Registered User** ) to take advantage of ParkWhiz's extensive benefits, you will be asked to provide a name, a telephone number, an email address, a password of your choice and your primary driving city. You may select not to receive emails from ParkWhiz (and/or from parking facilities which are part of the ParkWhiz Network), other than automated service messages pertaining to the information you may have requested (i.e. reservations, real-time status, availability). Where you have consented to receive marketing material from ParkWhiz and/or parking facilities at which you made a request and/or reservation, ParkWhiz will collect data on the category and location at which you have made the request in order to send you marketing communications which match your preferences. This can be accomplished via ParkWhiz's email opt-out function. You may also unsubscribe from the ParkWhiz email list at any time by sending an email to [unsubscribe@parkwhiz.com](mailto:unsubscribe@parkwhiz.com) and from a parking facility's email list by contacting them directly. 

You may be invited via email to provide feedback on your parking experience by completing a web-based Parking Feedback Form ("Feedback Form"). Parking feedback may be used to enhance the information on the ParkWhiz.com website and/or to let parking facilities know how they are doing. Any feedback you provide will be summarized with that of other drivers. Your feedback will not be publicized in a way that is attributable to you by name, email address, or other identifiable form. You may select not to receive future feedback invitation emails by following the "unsubscribe" instructions at the bottom of the Feedback Form. 

Parking facilities may receive summary reports of collective feedback from recent parking patrons. Any ratings you choose to provide based on your parking experience will be aggregated with those of other patrons so that they are not identifiable to you. If you provide comments about the parking facility, these may be shared with that facility but anonymously. 

If you express interest in receiving offers or information from ParkWhiz.com and our partners, we may occasionally send you e-mail or postal mail about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only ParkWhiz.com (or agents working on behalf of ParkWhiz.com and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers. 

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those ParkWhiz.com services that require the use of cookies in order to participate. 

ParkWhiz.com does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service. 

## How does ParkWhiz.com protect my personal financial information?

Keeping your personal financial information private is vitally important to us. As with all personal information, ParkWhiz.com will never rent or sell your personal financial information. Knowing that you use certain services or features may help us to offer you better and more relevant content and advertisements. But as with all personally identifiable information, we do not make this available to any third parties without your permission. 

Please note that there may be places on the ParkWhiz.com network of Web sites where you can transmit credit card information in order to complete a purchase transaction or for verification purposes. Any time we ask for a credit card number we transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format. We use industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. 

## Can I change my personal preferences?

Once a Registered User logs in to ParkWhiz.com, that user can view the personal information stored by ParkWhiz by clicking on the "Your Profile" link at the top of the page. In addition to being able to view your recent ParkWhiz reservation history, every user is also able to view and change the following personal information: name, email address, password, phone number, primary driving city, birthday (if it has been provided by the user), address (if it has been provided by the user), special requests that should be forwarded to parking facilties when making reservations (if they have been provided by the user), and whether that user would like to receive email from ParkWhiz. The user at anytime may request all personal information returned to the user, which may be accomplished by contacting ParkWhiz. 

## What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, ParkWhiz.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

## Additional Information

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to [privacy@parkwhiz.com](mailto:privacy@parkwhiz.com). 

Any changes to ParkWhiz's privacy policy will always be posted to this section of the web site, along with the effective date of the new policy. All users should check this privacy policy page periodically to stay abreast of any such changes. ParkWhiz will **never** make changes to its privacy policy that violates any applicable privacy laws or commercial privacy standards. 

If you have any questions or would like to provide feedback about ParkWhiz's privacy policy, please contact ParkWhiz via email at [info@parkwhiz.com](mailto:info@parkwhiz.com). You may also write directly to ParkWhiz, Attn: Legal Department, 208 S. Jefferson St, Suite 403, Chicago, IL 60661. 

Last modified on December 20, 2011.
